bizben.com 2012-06-22

# BizBen Privacy Policy | BizBen

Our policy on privacy is straightforward. In short, any information you submit to us will remain absolutely private and will not be shared with third-party companies. If you're interested in the lawyerly details, read on.

This website (the "Site") is operated by BizBen.com, a division of Business Exchange Network, Inc. This Privacy Statement (the "Statement") describes BizBen.com's collection, use and disclosure of information practices in connection with the Site.

For purposes of clarification, this Statement also describes BizBen.com's collection, use, and disclosure practices with respect to any personally identifiable information and Usage Data (as defined below) that is provided to BizBen.com

This Statement does not describe BizBen.com's collection, use and disclosure of information through means other than this Site (e.g., off-line) or the collection, use and disclosure practices of any Affiliate, third-party distribution partners or other third parties. For information on a third party's information collection, use and disclosure practices, please review the privacy policy on the applicable third party's website. Also, please note that this Site contains links to other websites. BizBen.com is not responsible for the websites, content or privacy practices of any third party. By using this Site, you acknowledge that you have read this Statement and agree that you are subject to the BizBen.com Terms of Service.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

You are not required to provide any personally identifiable information to visit the Site. BizBen.com automatically collects Usage Data (as described below) BizBen.com collects personally identifiable information only when you make it available through your use of the Site. You may be required to provide personally identifiable information to use certain services on this Site, including, but not limited to, the "Email Seller, Broker, or Resource" feature and to purchase and create a "Sell It Yourself" online listing ("SIY Ad") and account ("BizBen Power User Account"). In addition, you may submit personally identifiable information through the Site in other ways, including: (a) participating in online surveys, promotions, (b) subscribing to newsletters, editorial content, blog, podcast or news, (c) using the Site's "Feedback" and "More Information" forms; and (d) in connection with other products, services, features, or requests made available through the Site. The types of personally identifiable information that you provide will depend on the nature of the submission, but could include your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information.

**Passive Information Collection**

The Site automatically collects information and may also customize your visit through technical means, including the following:

**Cookies:** Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by computers (or servers) to identify your computer.

**Web Beacons:** Web beacons (also known as pixel tags, internet tags, clear GIFs, or single-pixel GIFs) are electronic images embedded into a webpage.

**IP Address Logs:** BizBen.com also logs Internet Protocol (IP) addresses - the location of your computer on the internet.

Cookies allow BizBen.com to recognize you when you visit the Site, to personalize your experience and generally to serve you better. For example, if you enter your name, address or email address on one of the Site's forms, it may be stored in a cookie so you do not have to enter it again on other forms on the Site. Cookies and web beacons can tell us what advertising you have seen on the Site, which allows BizBen.com to offer you a more diverse selection of advertising information and may also be used together to measure the effectiveness of BizBen.com advertising campaigns. Cookies, web beacons and IP addresses are also used to compile data regarding Site usage (what website you came from, what pages of the Site you visit, how long you were on the Site, what type of browser you are using, what website you went to, etc.). Web beacons may also be included in emails sent by BizBen.com to determine when and if such emails are opened or forwarded. You can disable cookies or otherwise manage them through tools provided with your browser software and with third-party software packages. If you turn off cookies, many of the Site's features will not work as well or at all. Anonymous information regarding use of our Site and services that is collected and/or aggregated by or on behalf of BizBen.com through the use of such technical means or otherwise is referred to in this Statement as "Usage Data."

**Information Use**

Personally Identifiable Information. Personally identifiable information collected by BizBen.com through your use of the Site may be stored on servers or in a cookie on your computer and may be used by BizBen.com for any of the following purposes:

To confirm or fulfill a request that you make (e.g., in order to send you information you have requested, BizBen.com may share your contact information with a participating BizBen.com business broker, agents, seller, resource).

To communicate with you regarding the BizBen.com service (e.g., BizBen.com may send you emails or call you to confirm a price quote request or to notify you that you have received a lead regarding a vehicle you have advertised or to request that you participate in a survey).

To send blog or podcast posts, business for sale updates, newsletters or other content via email or otherwise, but only if you have indicated that you wish to receive such materials

To improve your user experience.

For Site administration, analysis, research, development, optimization and other internal purposes, including, without limitation, to compile Usage Data.

As a responsible company, we believe obeying the law is important. Therefore, we may disclose personally identifiable information in order to comply with a subpoena or court order or when we are required to do so by law. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in cooperation with a law enforcement or government request. It is important for you to understand that the above policies and restrictions do not apply to our use or disclosure of your non-personally identifiable information.

**Usage Data:** Usage Data is used by BizBen.com for administrative, analytical, research, optimization and other purposes. For example, BizBen.com may use statistical analyses of Usage Data in order to measure interest in the various areas of the Site, for development purposes and to inform advertisers and partners in aggregate and anonymous terms about consumers who click on their advertising or other messages. IP addresses are also used for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.

With respect to promotional materials and reports that BizBen.com may send from time to time, BizBen.com will not continue to send you such communications if you ask us not to. However, you agree that BizBen.com may send to you, and you cannot opt out of, communications of a transactional or relationship nature, including, but not limited to, communications regarding fraudulent or illegal activity, the status of your BizBen.com Account, changes to this Statement or the BizBen.com Terms of Service, as well as communications to confirm, fulfill and follow up on your BizBen.com or Power User Account registration or a request submitted through the Site.

**Email a Page**

The Site offers you the ability to email certain pages of the Site to a friend or other third party. If you choose to use the "Email a Page" functionality, your name, email address and any message you are allowed to include will be visible to the recipient of the email. The "Email a Page" functionality is for informational purposes only and may not be used for any unlawful purpose, including any harassment or threats. Information collected by BizBen.com through the "Email a Page" functionality shall be used in accordance with this Statement.

**Changes to this Statement**

Any changes to this Statement will be posted on the Site in this location and this Statement will be identified as "Updated". Your continued use of the Site after such notice constitutes acceptance of such changes. In the event of such changes, you can then choose to do nothing, modify the personally identifiable information in your BizBen.com or Power User Account, change your email preferences or deactivate your BizBen.com or Power User Account Account.

**Security**

Your personally identifiable information is one of our most valuable assets. We take steps to keep it physically secure in our data centers and it is accessible only to authorized personnel as needed to perform operations governed by this policy. In addition, when BizBen.com collects credit card information from you, BizBen.com uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, the industry standard for protecting privacy in web transactions. Please keep in mind that despite these measures, BizBen.com cannot guarantee or warrant 100 percent security of its servers and databases. Moreover, BizBen.com cannot guarantee that personally identifiable information that you submit through the Site will not be intercepted or otherwise disclosed.

**Links**

This Site contains links to other sites. While BizBen.com encourages our business partners to adopt privacy policies that build users' trust and confidence in the internet, BizBen.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites linked to the Site or any third-party products or services offered through the Site.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this site, you indicate your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy then do not use this site. Your continued use of this site following any changes to this privacy policy constitutes your acceptance of such changes.

©2008 Business Exchange Network, BizBen.com, 7172 Regional Street, #290, Dublin, CA. 94568

Last updated on 2/3/09
